1. [Home](https://privacy.collegeboard.org/)
2. [Privacy Statement](https://privacy.collegeboard.org/privacy-statement)
3. Active Page: Access to Your Information and Data Retention

Access to Your Information and Data Retention
=============================================

 You can access your information and have certain choices on how to update and manage your information.

College Board will give you information about whether we have, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personally identifiable information, if reasonably available and subject to applicable laws.

We may keep your information as needed for legitimate educational purposes, to provide services to you or your educational institution, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Depending on where you live, you may have certain rights to request deletion of your personally identifiable information, subject to limitations and exceptions under applicable laws. College Board uses secure methods to delete or destroy personally identifiable information. 

If you have a College Board account, you may access and correct certain of your information by logging in to your account at [my.collegeboard.org/profile](https://my.collegeboard.org/profile). 

You can also ask us to close your College Board account. If College Board closes your account, you won’t be able to access your account. For students, this also means you will not be able to see or send any of your scores, or see information related to any other account activity. For educators, this also means you will lose your ability to access any of our programs or applications such as those used to administer College Board exams, AP teacher-related resources, and financial aid program tools. You’ll also be unsubscribed from optional communications and Student Search Service™, if applicable. Closing your account does not delete your information and you may request that College Board reactivate your account at a future date.

To make requests to access, correct, restrict, or delete your personally identifiable information or close your College Board account, please complete the [Your Privacy Choices webform](https://form.collegeboard.org/f/data-subject-rights-request?navId=gf-pc),  email us at [\[email protected\]](https://privacy.collegeboard.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or contact Customer Service. We’ll respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe and as required by applicable law.

Customer Service Contact Information:

College Board  
250 Vesey Street  
New York, NY 10281  
Phone: (844) 849-3551

See our [State Consumer Privacy Laws Supplemental Privacy Notice](https://privacy.collegeboard.org/node/256) for additional information about your rights in certain states. EEA, UK and Brazil residents—see our [EEA, UK and Brazil Privacy Notice](https://privacy.collegeboard.org/node/66) for additional information about your rights.

Related Topics
--------------

Related Topics
--------------
